JANUS QUEK

• DETAILS •

Singapore +65 81898717 janus.quek@gmail.com

> Place of birth Singapore

Nationality Singaporean

• LINKS •

https://janusquek.tech/ https://linkedin.com/in/janus-quek/

• SKILLS •

C++

C#

Python

Unity

Unreal Engine

Microsoft Office

Adobe Photoshop

• LANGUAGES •

English

Chinese

Japanese

• HOBBIES •

Video Gaming Story Writing Music Composition

PROFILE

Experienced in C# Scripting Integration via Mono, adaptive audio technology via FMod, editor programming via IMGUI, serialization via Rapidjson, memory management, and gameplay programming via C# scripting.

Attained various academic achievements and project awards during my time in Digipen.

Currently on a scholarship with The Infocomm Media Development Authority of Singapore.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Game Design, DigiPen Institute of Technology Singapore, Singapore

September 2018 — August 2022

GPA: 3.71

Admitted into the Director's List every semester

Helped develop Howl: A Tale of Wolves in 2019:

Awarded 3rd Place for Claude Comair Grand Prize for Game of the Year

Awarded Best Sophomore Game

Awarded Best Sophomore Technology

Finalist for Best 2D Graphics Technology

Finalist for Most Innovative Design

Helped develop Spellthief in 2018:

Awarded Best Freshman Technology

Finalist for Best 2D Physics Technology

Finalist for Best Music and Sound Design

Finalist for Best Artificial Intelligence

Game and Entertainment Technology, Temasek Polytechnic, Singapore

April 2013 — March 2016

Admitted into the Director's List for AY2013/2014 October semester

Contracted by the school after graduation to work on a game for research purposes

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

National Serviceman at National Service, Singapore

October 2016 — August 2018

Programmer Intern at Bandai Namco Studios Singapore, Singapore

October 2015 — March 2016

Worked on a prototype of a new game idea in Unreal Engine 4

Worked with both Blueprints and C++ on Unreal Engine 4

Worked with WPF in C# in developing a time-in time-out software

Worked with MySQL to create a database to work in conjunction with said software

¶ REFERENCES

References available upon request